Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Press releases, subject files, 1974-2002; 2006; Series II.; 7.08 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
  - Foundation:
    - Grants:
      - Gifts to LA Institutions, California Community Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 21)
        [Note: Includes 10/1/1987 Release on 8 Million in Gifts to Los Angeles Institutions; Press clips; Press packet including fact sheet, 4/11/1988 release on Big Help Arrives for Artists and Organizations, Artistic Fellowship Program with 1988 application, and Existing and Innovative Grant Progam with 1988 application]
      - 1986 Gifts to Los Angeles Institutions, October 30, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 22)
      - 1985 Gifts to Los Angeles Institutions, October 23, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 23)
      - Buffalo State College Release: Receives Getty Grant of $33,750, January 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 70)
      - College News Service Release: $500,000 Gift to Buffalo State College, July 31, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 72)
      - Fine Arts Training Programs Grants, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 73)
        [Note: Includes Draft of memorandum summarizing program in detail, 5/16/1985; University of Delaware release, "University of Delaware Receives Challenge Grant", 12/9/1985; Letter from University of Delaware regarding preferred wording for release; Letter to Andrew Mellon Foundation summarizing meeting, 5/17/1985; Release regarding funding for three fine arts training programs, 5/22/1985]
      - Assorted Gifts and Grants, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 71)
        [Note: Includes Smithsonian release, "National Institute for the Conservation of Cultural Property Receives Getty Grant", 8/1985; Wayne State University release, "Wayne State Receives Getty Grant", 8/1/1985 (1 draft copy); Letter to University of Delaware about $3000 Grant from Getty, 5/21/1985; Press clipping regarding Northeast Document Conservation Center Grant of $117,000]
      - 1984 Gifts to Los Angeles Institutions (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 24)
        [Note: Includes 10/16/1984 Press Release; 8/27/1984 Memorandum on Announcement of Grant and Gifts Programs; 10/9/1984 Memorandum on Answers to Questions Regarding Grant and Gift Releases; 10/10/1984 Memorandum on Answers to Questions on Gifts and Grants; Press clips]
      - Drafts of Assorted Press Releases from Outside Institutions that Have Received Grants (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 76)
    - Grant totals:
      - Las Organizaciones Dedicadas Al Arte..., May 11, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 77)
      - LA Collections Online: Grant for Electronic Cataloguing at 11 Local Arts Institutes, January 27, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 78)
      - Local Grant to Support the Arts Passport Program, March 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 79)
      - $11.5 Million Awarded in 114 Countries During 1993-1995, November 7, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 80)
      - $7.5 Million Awarded in 51 Countries During 1992-1993, April 8, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 81)
        [Includes: Press Releases showing breakdown of 1992-1993 awards: DM222,000 Awarded in Germany; FF1,130,000 Awarded in France; $600,000 Awarded in Italy; £600,000 Awarded in England]
      - $1.3 Million Awarded Central/Eastern Europe Art History and Conservation Projects, June 17, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 88)
      - $5.3 Million Awarded in 28 Countries During 1991-1992, March 4, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 89)
      - Support for Eastern Europe: $535,000 Art Scholarship and Conservation Grants, May 5, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 82)
      - $5.5 Million Awarded in Seventeen Countries 1990-1991, October 31, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 83)
      - $6.5 Millions Awarded in Eleven Countries 1989-1990, December 21, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 84)
      - 2 Million Pounds Awarded in UK Since 1984, January 19, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 85)
      - $20 Million Awarded Since 1984, December 21, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 86)
      - List of Grants Awarded 7/1/1988 to 6/30/1989, 1988-1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 87)
    - Multicultural internships:
      - Getty and Los Angeles County Offer 305 Paid Summer Internships in the Arts, April 6, 2001 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 105)
      - LA Museums and Visual Arts Org. Seek Multicultural Undergrads for Summer Intern, April 1, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 104)
      - Internships for Culturally Diverse Students, January 20, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 104)
      - Multicultural Internships Awarded to LA Area Arts Organizations, April 16, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 106)
      - Funding for Summer Multicultural Internships, March 25, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 107)
      - Internships for Students of Culturally Diverse Backgrounds, January 12, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 105)
      - Funding Offered for Multicultural Interns, November 30, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 108)
      - Fact Sheet: LA Area Colledge Students Explore Careers in the Arts, July 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 109)
      - 15 Undergraduates Named for Summer Internships, June 19, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 106)
      - $323,000 to Local Arts Organizations: Summer Multicultural Interships Funded, March 22, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 110)
      - Multicultural Internships, 1995, January 11, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 107)
      - Multicultural Internships for Local Museums and Visual Arts, December 21, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 111)
      - Naming Summer Interns, July 13, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 108)
      - $290,000 Awarded to Local Museums and Visual Arts Groups, March 8, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 112)
      - Undergraduate Summer Internships, January 27, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 109)
      - Multicultural Internships for Locals Museums and Visual Arts, December 10, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 113)
      - First Undergraduate Summer Internships Announced, June 25, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 110)
      - Over $250,000 Awarded to Local Museums and Visual Arts Groups, April 20, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 114)
      - Internships Reflecting Cultural Diversity Offered this Summer, March 11, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 111)
      - Multicultural Internships for Local Museums and Arts Groups, March 3, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 115)
    - Postdoctoral fellowships (Fellowships for History for Art and Humanities):
      - Grant Program Postdoctoral Fellowships, June 4, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 90)
      - Grant Program Postdoctoral Fellowships, May 13, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 91)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships Awarded, April 16, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 92)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships Awarded, April 16, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 93)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships Awarded, May 15, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 94)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships and Senior Research Grants Awarded, June 30, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 95)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships and Senior Research Grants Awarded, August 24, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 96)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships and Senior Research Grants Awarded, May 5, 1992; (includes Hood College 5/29/1992) (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 97)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships and Senior Research Grants Awarded, April 17, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 98)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships and Research Grants Awarded, April 4, 1990; (includes diskette) (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 99)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships and Senior Research Grants Announced, April 4, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 100)
      - Postdoctoral Fellowships Announced, April 25, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 101)
      - Woodrow Wilson Foundation Release: 20 Scholars Receive First Postdoctoral Fellowships, March 12, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-4, Folder 111)
  - Publications:
    - Trust:
      - Lawrence Alma Tadema: Spring, July 25, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 33)
      - The Art of Seeing: An Interpretation of the Aesthetic Encounter, June 3, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 34)
      - Release and Review Information: Looking at Prints, Drawings, and Watercolors, February 14, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 35)
      - Release and Review Information: Edvard Munch: Starry Night, February 14, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 36)
      - Release and Review Information: Masterpieces of Painting, October 7, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 37)
      - Guide to the Villa and Its Gardens, October 7, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 38)
    - Museum:
      - Jacques-Louis David: The Farewell of Telemachus and Eucharis, circa 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 39)
      - House of Eternity: The Tomb of Nefertari, October 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 40)
      - Doris Ulmann, Photographs from the Getty Museum, April 9, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 41)
      - Anthony van Dyck: Thomas Howard, The Earl of Arundel, February 2, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 42)
      - Walker Evans: The Getty Museum Collection, November 6, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 43)
      - Arts of Isfahan: Diversity and Identity in 17th Century Perisa, October 24, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 44)
      - In Focus: Alfred Steiglitz, October 17, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 45)
      - Aldus Manutius: Printer and Publisher of Renaissance Venice, September 12, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 46)
      - "If..." Sarah Perry, Artist and Author, September 12, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 47)
      - The Town Of Hercules: A Buried Treasure Trove, September 12, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 48)
      - Aldus Manutius: Printer and Publisher of Renaissance Venice, September 12, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 49)
      - Masterpieces of Painting in the Getty, August 4, 1995; August 22, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 50)
      - In Focus: Laszlo Moholy-Nagy Centennial, June 27, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1)
        [Note: Listed in Museum department under "Photography"]
      - Edgar Degas: Waiting / Joachim Wtewael: Mars and Venus Surprised by Vulcan, May 25, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 51)
      - Fact Sheet and Order Form: Make Your Own Museum: An Activity Package for Children, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 52)
      - A Literary Companion to Greece, November 15, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 53)
      - A Passion for Antiquities: Fleischman Collection, April 29, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 54)
        [Note: Release is identical to July 27, 1994 copy listed in Museum department under "Antiquities" under "Fleischman Collection"]
      - The Hours of Simon de Varie, March 8, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 55)
      - Pioneers of Landscape Photography, January 25, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 56)
      - Looking at European Ceramics, September 15, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 57)
      - Albert Renger-Patzsch: Joy Before the Object, September 15, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 58)
      - Camille Silvy: "River Scene, France", January 8, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 59)
      - Mira Calligraphiae Monumenta: A 16th Century Manuscript, July 20, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 60)
      - Disciples of Light: Photographs in the Brewster Album, June 3, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 61)
      - Interactive Videodisc on Illuminated Manuscripts, May 2, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 62)
      - Release and Review Copy: European Drawings I, April 20, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 63)
      - Interactive Videodisc Fact Sheet, August 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 64)
      - Release and Review Copy: New Monograph on Photographs Book: Whisper of the Muse, December 8, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 65)
    - Center for the History and Art in the Humanities / Getty Research Institute:, 1989-1997:
      - Publications Program of Getty Research Institute Honered by AIA "Publisher of the Year" Award, December 23, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 66)
      - Topkapi Book Scroll, March 21, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 67)
      - CHAH Architecture Book Award, June 20, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 68)
      - The Los Angeles Watts Towers, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 69)
      - RES Anthropology and Aesthetics, April 30, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 70)
      - Otto Wagner's Modern Architecture, June 6, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 71)
    - Getty Conservation Institute:
      - Picture LA – Landmarks of a New Generation, May 28, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-4)
        [Note; The Press Release is filed under the Getty Conservation Institute under "Exhibits" and "Picture LA"]
      - Publication of Earthquake Handbook, October 7, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 72)
    - Art History Information Program:
      - Pacific Visions Release: Bibliography of the History of Art, February 21, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5)
        [Note: Press Release is located under Art History Information Program under the listing "Bibliography of the History of Art"]
    - Getty Center for Education in the Arts (GCEA)/Getty Education Institute (GEI):
      - A Guide to Discipline-Based Art Education, January 13, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 111)
      - The Quiet Revolution: Changing the Face of Arts Education, March 6, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 112)
      - Celebrating Pluralism: Art, Education, and Cultural Diversity, September 13, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 113)
      - The Intelligent Eye, July 21, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 114)
      - Discipline-Based Art Education and Cultural Diveristy (1 copy), March 21, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 115)
      - New Report: Improving Visual Arts Education, October 8, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 116)
      - Reinventing the Wheel: A Design for Student Achievement, January 25, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 117)
      - New Kit: Be Smart, Include Art: A Planning Kit for PTA's, August 17, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 118)
      - NSBA News Release: More Than Pumpkins in October: Visual Literacy, May 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 119)
      - The Discipline-Based Art Education Handbook, February 26, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 120)
      - New Publication Series: Art Education: A Critical Necessity, September 6, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 121)
      - Curriculum Sampler Published, July 31, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 122)
- Press kits, 1954; 1973,; 1983-1984,; 1989-2020; Series III.; 12.69 Linear Feet (24 boxes)
  These press kits document events that the J. Paul Getty Museum and the J. Paul Getty Trust wished to publicize to media outlets, and date from 1954, 1973, 1983 to 1984, and 1989 to 2018. The press kits were distributed to journalists and other members of the media by the J. Paul Getty Museum (1954-1982), the Department of Public Affairs (1983-1999), and the Communications Department (2000-present) at exhibition openings, press conferences, and other events organized to promote Getty activities. The press kits were also distributed upon request. Although the kits contain press releases that may be found in Series I. Chronological press releases and Series II. Press releases, subject files, these records are unique in that they comprise illustrated folders containing complete sets of publicity documentation for exhibitions or events that include fact sheets, images approved for reproduction in third-party publications, exhibition object lists, lists of related publications, public events, and other information.
  While the majority of the press kits concern exhibitions, topics also include acquisitions; collaborative initiatives, including Pacific Standard Time (PST) 2014 and 2018; conferences; conservation initiatives; buildings and grounds; general kits providing information about the Getty Center and its programs; theater productions; and the tenth and twentieth anniversaries of the Brentwood Getty Center. Of note are the press kits for the original 1954 opening of the J. Paul Getty Museum located in Mr. Getty's Ranch House, and various kits documenting the building of the Getty Center in Brentwood, including site and architect selection, center design, construction, and the 1997 opening. All Getty programs, including those no longer in operation, are represented.
  Two kits for each event have been collected when possible. While the number of press kits is extensive, it is not presumed to be a comprehensive collection.
  Records are arranged chronologically by year.
  - 1954, 1973:
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum, 1954 (Box 2019.IA.03-02, Folder 1)
      Includes documents announcing the opening of the museum on April 24th, 1954, and descriptions of the galleries.
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum, 1973 (Box 2019.IA.03-02, Folder 2)
      Includes three informational packets and loose press releases dated 1974.
  - 1980s:
    - The J. Paul Getty Trust to build, 1983 (Box 2019.IA.03-02, Folder 3)
      Press kit announcing intention to build a complex of structures consisting of a Center for the History of Art and the Humanities, a Conservation Institute, and a new Museum.
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum press information, 1983-1985; undated (Box 2019.IA.03-02, Folder 4)
      Includes press releases announcing formation of the programs and job appointments to various senior-level positions.
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum press information, 1984; undated (Box 2019.IA.03-02, Folder 5)
      Includes fact sheet on the museum, J. Paul Getty, the board of trustees, and senior staff.
    - Renaissance Painting in Manuscripts, Treasures from the British Library, October 6, 1983-January 8, 1984 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
      Kit contains branded folder and stationary only.
    - Construction of Getty Center press kit, August 11, 1989; March 21, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 5)
      Includes 8/11/1989 Release on First Phase of Construction Underway, 3/21/1991 Fact Sheet on Building Program, and Photos of Architectural Models with Captions.
  - 1990:
    - Abode 90, International Conference on the Conservation of Earthen Architecture, October 14, 1990-October 19, 1990 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 1991:
    - Anyone, May 10-11, 1991
      Press kit for a two-day event co-sponsored by the Getty Center for the History of Art in the Humanities to launch an annual publication project and an Institution Without Walls.
    - Richard Meier's design for the Getty Center, October 1991; undated (Box 2019.IA.03-02)
      Includes images of Getty Center architectural models and design drawings.
    - Invitation to press briefing and luncheon to present the design and model of the Getty Center, October 1991 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
  - 1992:
    - Art on Film, Film on Art, October 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-02)
    - Conservation of the Tomb of Tutankhamun, September 23, 1992 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 1993:
    - Conservation of Ancient Sites on the Silk Road, October 03, 1993-October 08, 1993 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 1994:
    - A Passion For Antiquities, Ancient Art From the Collection of Barbara and Lawrence Fleischman, October 13, 1994-January 15, 1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
    - Picture L.A,, Landmarks Of A New Generation, December 7, 1994-January 6, 1995 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - The Getty Art History Information Program, 1994 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Richard Meier's Design for the Getty Center, 1994 (Box 2020.IA.04-02)
      Updated version of Richard Meier's Design for the Getty Center 1991 press kit.
  - 1995:
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum press information, 1995-1996 (Box 2020.IA.04-02)
  - 1996:
    - Picture Cape Town, Landmarks Of A New Generation, November 20, 1996-January 5, 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - The Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities, March 1996 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 1997:
    - Getty Center opening press kit, 1997:
      - The Getty Center [enclosure style 1] (Box 2019.IA.03-02)
        Includes slide images of the site and galleries. Photographers: John Stephens, S. Francis/Esto, Tom Bonner, The J. Paul Getty Trust.
      - The Getty Center [enclosure style 2] (Box 2019.IA.03-02)
      - The Getty Center ephemera bag (Box 2001.IA.06-01)
    - Getty Center, Getty Program, and J. Paul Getty Museum photo captions, 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
      Includes slides. Also includes lists of descriptive captions corresponding to each slide, and image credits.
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum press information, 1997 (Box 2020.IA.04-02)
    - Celebrating the Opening of the Getty Center in December 1997 for Community Group Leaders Press Kit, September 26, 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - J. Paul Getty Museum in Malibu Set to Close Temporarily on July 6, 1997, February 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Picture Mexico City, Landmarks of a New Generation, September 4- October 26, 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - Picture Mumbai, Landmarks of a New Generation, January 21, 1997-March 02, 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - L.A. Culture Net, Your Link to a World of Arts and Culture, April 1997 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 1998:
    - The Getty Education Institute for the Arts, 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-01)
    - Bay Area Video Coalition, May-June 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-02)
      Press kit for the Bay Area Video Coalition's publication Mediamaker Handbook, for which the Getty provided support.
    - Picture Paris, Landmarks of a New Generation, April 21, 1998-May 12, 1998 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 1999:
    - Como Visitar el Getty, 1999
      General information press kit in Spanish language.
    - Martin Puryear, That Profile, a new sculpture for the Getty Center, November 23, 1999-January 9, 2000 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Edgar Degas: Photographer, February 2-March 28, 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-02)
    - Dosso Dossi, Court Painter in Renaissance Ferrara, April 27-July 11, 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Adriaen de Vries, Imperial Sculptor, October 12, 1999-January 9, 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Nadar Warhol, Paris New York, July 20, 1999-October 10, 1999 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
  - 2000:
    - Poussin Landscapes by Leon Kossoff, January 18-April 16, 2000 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - Carlton Watkins: From Where the View Looked Best, February 15-June 4, 2000 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - Departures, 11 Artists at the Getty, February 29-May 7, 2000 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
    - Departures, 11 Artists at the Getty press preview, February 29-May 7, 2000 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - Painting on Light, July 11-September 24, 2000 (Box 2018.IA.03-01)
      Co-organized with the Saint Louis Art Museum
    - Raphael and His Circle, Drawings from Windsor Castle, October 31, 2000- January 7, 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - The Queen of the Angels, August 15-November 5, 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - The Gualenghi-d'Est Hours: Art and Devotion in Renaissance Ferrara, May 9-July 30, 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Edible Monument, February 26, 2000-May 21, 2000 (Box 2019.IA.03-12)
  - 2001:
    - The Getty, 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
      General information about the Getty Center.
    - The J. Paul Getty Museum quarterly news bulletin and exhibition schedule, Spring 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - Shaping the Great City, Modern Architecture in Central Europe, 1890-1937, February 20-May 5, 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - A Royal Menagerie: Porcelain Animals from Dresden, To Create a Living Art: 19th Century Drawings, May 1-July 15, 2001 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - Walker Evans, Before and After, July 10-October 28, 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)
    - The Armenian Gospels of Gladzor, September 11-December 2, 2001 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - Devices of Wonder, From the World in a Box to Images on a Screen, November 13, 2001-February 3, 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-10)
    - Manuel Alvarez Bravo: Optical Parables, November 13, 2001-February 17, 2002 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - [Getty Center Press Kit], January 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - Media Pop Conference, David Tudor Symposium, Spring 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
    - Harry Smith Symposium, April 20, 2001-April 21, 2001 (Box 2019.IA.03-13)
  - 2002:
    - Getty Center press kit, 2002 (Box 2021.IA.29-26)
    - Italy and the Grand Tour, February 5-August 11, 2002 (Box 2019.IA.03-03)